Mohammad H. Ghasemzadeh, PMP

408-667-9312 • 88 San Fernando St. Suite 1906, San Jose CA • hosein88@gmail.com

Summary

Mohammad has launched three start-ups (two mobile apps and one web app) from scratch to over 50,000 users and counting. Mohammad has also worked as a strategy and operations consultant, helping clients improve their operations, increase sales, satisfy regulatory requirements and cultivate innovation within their organization.

Professional Experiences

Co-Founder, CardStak Inc. SEP 2014 – PRESENT

• CardStak.com is used for networking events hosted by UC Berkeley Haas School of Business, Engineering & Law School. It has 10K+ users and helped numerous students, alumni and professionals get acquainted and build new relationships Skills: Entrepreneurship, Agile Product Management, Google Analytics, Amazon AWS

PricewaterhouseCoopers Management Consulting TORONTO, CANADA Senior Strategy Consultant, DEC 2012 - MAR 2014

- Executed global market scan regarding best practices in mortgage lending and developed recommendations for improving sales and customer experience. Presented analysis to executives and received approval for implementation
- Analyzed survey responses from approximately two thousand executives and developed the Canadian Edition for PwC Global Innovation study with insights on executive plans, mindsets and investments in innovation
- Helped a Credit Union achieve efficiencies through developing a model for customer segmentation, building standardized practices for business centers and other tactical improvements

Skills: Strategy, Leadership, Big Data Analytics, Presentation, Relationship Management

Bank of Montreal Financial Group Toronto, Canada

Operations Consultant, OCT 2011 - NOV 2012

- Delivered lean training and crafted training material as part of Operations Management Program for senior managers
- Developed a library of information on previous projects utilizing best practices, allowing consultants to leverage knowledge gained during previous projects for future projects
- Designed a training and selection process for new recruits within Product Operations resulting in 25% less error rates <u>Skills</u>: Operations Management, Data Analysis, Presentation

Co-Founder, Smartiky Apps SEP 2009 – SEP 2011

- Launched two mobile apps and one web app with an aggregate user-base of over 50,000 users
 - o Smart Mail (http://tinyurl.com/og6wmbr). This app allows users to delete content of sent email messages, notifies users when email message has been read and creates beautiful templates for messages
 - o Smart Poll (http://tinyurl.com/pewkwmp). This was a mobile system for crowdsourcing opinions and was featured on numerous blogs and app review websites. This app used Facebook APIs

Skills: Agile Product Management, Full Stack Development, Android Java, SQL, Photoshop, Needs and usability assessment

Education

UC Berkeley (Berkeley, USA), Master of Information & Management Systems, 2014 - Present

- 1st place and audience award UC Berkeley Haas PLAY Hackathon (largest student-run tech conference in the Country)
- · Graduate Student instructor for two courses: Principles of Business, Applied innovation at Haas School of Business

Sharif University of Technology (Tehran, Iran), B.Sc. Computer Engineering - Software, 2004 - 2008

Interests

- Excellent snowboarder and basketball player (won numerous inter-collegiate titles)
- Expert in creating designs with Adobe Photoshop over 9 years of experience